const quiz1data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "Would you mind __ the window?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "opening", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "to open", isCorrect: false},
     ],
      help: 'Phrases with mind followed by the -ing form. '
   },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "I enjoy ___ football.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to play", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "playing", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Verbs of liking and disliking such as: enjoy, hate, fancy, like, love etc are followed by the -ing form.'
   },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "When you leave the hotel, please leave your key ___ reception?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "at", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "in", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'Verb + “to verb” is pushing to the future. This means that its abstract (not “real”) and that means it can feel “philosophical.” Its usually a goal (not a process).Verb + “-ing” is more “real,” based on experience and is usually a process (not a goal).'
   },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "I recommend _____ by train.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to not travelling", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "not travelling", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by -ing: stop, finish, imagine, suggest, recommend, avoid, mind, miss, risk, enjoy. The negative form is verb + not + ing.'
   },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Henry decided ___ his appointment with the dentist.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to cancel", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "cancelling", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: choose, decide, expect, forget, hope, intend, learn, prefer, plan, remember, want etc.'
   },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "I prefer ___ alone.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to travel", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "travelling", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: choose, decide, expect, forget, hope, intend, learn, prefer, plan, remember, want etc.'
   },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Sally planned ____ a holiday.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to take", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "taking", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: choose, decide, expect, forget, hope, intend, learn, prefer, plan, remember, want etc.'
   },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "He admitted ___ my money.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to steal", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "stealing", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by -ing: stop, recommend, admit, avoid, imagine, finish, consider, deny, risk, fancy etc'
   },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "If you gamble, you risk ___ your money.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "losing", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "to lose", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by -ing: stop, recommend, admit, avoid, imagine, finish, consider, deny, risk, fancy etc'
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "David forgot ___ the door.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "locking", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "to lock", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: choose, decide, expect, forget, hope, intend, learn, prefer, plan, remember, want etc.'
    },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: "I haven't finished ___ my essay. ",
        answersList: [
          {answer: "to write", isCorrect: false},
          {answer: "writing", isCorrect: true},
        ],
        help: 'Some verbs that are followed by -ing: stop, recommend, admit, avoid, imagine, finish, consider, deny, risk, fancy etc'
    },
      {
        id: 12,
        question: "George expected ___ late.",
        answersList: [
          {answer: "being", isCorrect: false},
          {answer: "to be", isCorrect: true},
        ],
        help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: choose, decide, expect, forget, hope, intend, learn, prefer, plan, remember, want etc.'
    },
  ]
export default quiz1data
